<Document>
# Standard Operating Procedure
Standard Operating Procedures, commonly referred to as SOPs, are written expectations as to the function and performance of the many jobs on NT-CC Consortium space stations. They serve two purposes, one in-character, and one out-of-character.

## In-Character
In-character, SOPs are the requirements written by NanoTrasen for Central Command for their contractors and sub-contractors.

They are NanoTrasen's expectations for your behaviour, and breaking them makes Central Command look bad in NanoTrasen's eyes, something they'd prefer to avoid.

As such, while SOP is not of Central Command's making, they will enforce it unless there's something greater to be gained.

One of the NanoTrasen Representative's primary objectives is to ensure adherence to these contractual obligations, and they are an authority on the matter.

## Out-of-Character
Out of character, SOP provides the bare-minimum expectations for what you should be able to accomplish in your position.

[color=#a4885c][bold]If what is written in SOP doesn't sound like something you are willing or able to do, then you should not be playing that job.[/bold][/color]

SOPs are [bold]not[/bold] server rules, but routinely ignoring them puts you potentially in violation of [textlink="Server Rule #6" link="RuleSL6"], as your character would have been fired long ago and therefore doesn't make sense in-character as a continued employee.

As Command and Security, you are expected to adhere more closely to these bare-minimum requirements, as is laid out in [textlink="Server Rule #13" link="RuleSL13"]

## Non-Standard Situations
With that being said, nobody would be following workplace regulations if there's an active shooter, and the same goes for Space Station 14.

Your character, unless they are trained to handle such situations (such as Security and Command), is not at all expected to behave rationally during times of crisis.

Your character should, above all, [bold]value their own life[/bold], regulations be damned. Hiding in lockers or on the ATS, assembling makeshift weapons and barricading your department, whatever you can imagine as long as it does not constitute [textlink="Validhunting" link="RuleSL8"].
</Document>
