<Document>
# Head of Security

<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ToyFigurineHeadOfSecurity" Caption="Head of Security"/>

### §1\n
Standard [color=#00a933]Code Green[/color] equipment is:

<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponSubMachineGunWt550"/>
	or
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponEnergySMG"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Stunbaton"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HoloprojectorSecurity"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FlashlightSeclite"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RadioHandheldSecurity"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CombatKnife"/>
	in
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingShoesBootsJack"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GrenadeFlashBang"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TearGasGrenade"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Handcuffs"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Zipties"/>
</Box>

- 2.\n
The Head of Security is subject to both Security and Command SOP. If overlapping, Security SOP takes precedence.
- 3.\n
The Head of Security is first and foremost the leader of the Security Department.\n\n
3.1\n
They are responsible for the proper adherence to SOP and Corporate Law of their entire department.\n\n
3.2\n
They are responsible for the coordination of their department, particularly during times of crisis.\n\n
3.3\n
They are responsible for staying informed on matters of station safety, and must be able and willing to inform the crew as to the reasons for elevated threat levels.\n\n
3.4\n
They are responsible for covering staff shortages in their department, using the following methods in order of preference:\n\n
3.4.1\n
Re-assignment of existing security members.\n\n
3.4.2\n
Recruitment of new security members.\n\n
3.4.3\n
Performing the duties of missing subordinates on their own.
- 4.\n
The Head of Security may not engage in regular Security Officer activities if these prevent them from properly upholding §3.
- 5.\n
The Head of Security must not have any disabilities or ailments, such as muteness, that overly prohibit them from upholding §3.
- 6.\n
The Head of Security should refrain from combat operations unless tactically necessary, instead ensuring the strategic cohesion of their department as per §3.
- 7.\n
The Head of Security is cleared to confine sentenced criminals in the Brig for up to 30 minutes.\n\n
7.1\n
The Head of Security is furthermore allowed to overrule the sentences of other members of Security as long as the sentence hasn't already been handed out to the detainee.
</Document>
