<Document>
# Warden

<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ToyFigurineWarden" Caption="Warden"/>

### §1 Standard Code Green Equipment

<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Stunbaton"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponPistolDP"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WeaponEnergyShotgun"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="HoloprojectorSecurity"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FlashlightSeclite"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RadioHandheldSecurity"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CombatKnife"/>
	in
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingShoesBootsJack"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GrenadeFlashBang"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="TearGasGrenade"/>
</Box>
<Box>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Handcuffs"/>
	<GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Zipties"/>
</Box>

### §2 Stewardship of the Brig
- 1.\n
The Warden is responsible for the state of the brig, and must see to it that it is properly maintained.
- 2.\n
The Warden is responsible for the well-being of the prisoners inside the brig, and must see to it that they are treated properly.
- 3.\n
The Warden is responsible for the containment of said prisoners as well, including:\n\n
3.1\n
Confiscating weapons and break-out equipment from prisoners.\n\n
3.2\n
Restraining and subduing rioting prisoners as is necessary.

### §3 Prosecution
- 1.\n
The Warden acts as security's primary prosecutor during normal sentencing.
- 2.\n
The Warden is cleared to confine sentenced criminals for up to [bold]20 minutes[/bold].
- 3.\n
The Warden is responsible for ensuring that Criminal Records are kept properly up to date and that Security Officers properly document their sentences.
- 4.\n
The Warden is to remain attentive to their radio at all times, as their approval is critical to sentencing.\n\n
4.1\n
The Warden must not have any disabilities or ailments preventing them from fulfilling this duty.

### §4 Stewardship of the Armoury
- 1.\n
The Warden is responsible for the tidiness and organisation of the Armoury.
- 2.\n
The Warden is responsible for properly locking away contraband and returned weaponry.
- 3.\n
The Warden is responsible for the safety of the Armoury, such as the proper configuration of its internal turrets, and the maintenance of its structural integrity.
- 4.\n
The Warden is cleared to file and approve permits for the issuing of armoury equipment on [color=#2a6099]Code Blue[/color].
- 5.\n
The Warden may hand out armoury equipment freely on [color=#ff0000]Code Red[/color].
- 6.\n
The Warden is responsible for the retrieval of armoury equipment that is no longer needed once states of emergency end.


### §5
- 1.\n
Paragraphs §2, §3 and §4 necessitate remaining in the Security Department, and the Warden should therefore not leave said department without permission from the Head of Security, or during emergencies.

</Document>
